我的姐姐...
My sister...
她刚刚...
was just-
我的上帝，都发生了什么事啊？
Oh, God. What happened?
她到底怎么了？
What happened to her?
时间轴 特效：lengshan310
惹鬼回路之二
...安全区域。这不是演习
...regional safe zones. This is not a test.
- 贾丝汀?   - 重复，这不是演习
- Justine?  - Repeat. This is not a test.
贾丝汀！
Justine!
贾丝汀，你在哪儿？
Justine, where are you?
贾丝汀，妈妈在这里
Justine, it's me. It's Mommy.
嗨
Hello?
里面有人吗？
Hello? Is anyone there?
拜托了  开下门
Hello?  Please.
我是431房的邻居，快开门
I'm your neighbor from 431 . Please.
我需要帮助，我的女儿找不到了！
Please, I need some help. I can't find my daughter.
喂！喂！
Hello! Hello!
拜托开下门！
Please open the door!
求你了
Please.
求求你们
帮帮我
Please help me.
快开门！帮帮我！
Open the door! Help me, please. Help me.
天哪
Oh, my God.
是瘟疫
It's a plague.
米歇尔?
Michelle?
我的天
Oh, my- Oh, my God.
对不起，发生了恐怖的事情，我的女儿不见了
E-Excuse me. Something terrible's happened, and I can't find my daughter.
我的小女儿不见了
I-I've lost my little girl.
- 能不能告诉我这里到底发生什么事了？ - 我为什么要那么做？
- Please. Can you tell me what's going on here? - Why would I do that?
什么？
I- I'm sorry?
- 就这样下去吧 - 我不明白
- Go on like this. - I don't understand.
太痛了
It hurts.
痛得要命
It- It hurts so bad.
哪儿疼？怎么啦？
What hurts? What's wrong with you?
你不会明白的，你怎么可能体会到呢
You wouldn't understand. I mean, how- how could you really?
- 是的，对不起 - 丽莎. 丽莎快回话
- You're right. I-I'm sorry. I don't. - Lisa. Lisa, answer me.
- 告诉我你在哪儿 - 真对不起，我想...
- Tell me where you are. - Oh, God. I'm sorry. I- I thought-
已经回不去了
It's not enough to.
就耽搁你一会儿好吗？我的女儿不见了
Can I just have a moment of your time, please? I've lost my little girl.
我不活了...我就想去死...
I wanna die. I just wanna die.
- （电话中）丽莎，一定会有办法的... - 我已经不知道怎么办了
-  Lisa, it's time to get you help. - But I don't know how.
- 抱歉打搅你... - （电话中）会有办法的，告诉我你在哪儿
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - I can help you.Just tell me where you are.
不好意思，我只是想找到我的女儿，没别的...
I'm sorry. I have to find my little girl. I'm sorry.
（电话中）赶快告诉我你在哪儿，我正到处找你呢！
All you have to do is tell me where you are. I've looked everywhere.
- 永别了，戴维- （电话中）别挂电话，听我说...
- Good-bye, David. - No. Don't hang up. Stay on the line.
- 永别... - 丽莎，你在哪里？
- Good-bye. - Lisa, where are you?
米歇尔，有什么事吗？
What do you want, Michelle?
感谢上帝，卡尔曼婶婶， 我还以为你和佩特叔叔也已经...
Aunt Carmen. Oh, God. I thought you and Uncle Pete were-
- 卡尔曼婶婶？ - 你不应该这个时候还外出的
- Carmen? - You shouldn't be out at this hour.
太不对劲了
Something terrible is happening.
- 到处都... - 我知道
- Everywhere you look- - I know.
贾丝汀也不见了
Justine's gone.
我突然希望...
And- Well, I thought, um-
希望我是把她放在你这里了
I thought maybe I left her with you.
没有啊，她没有...
No. She's- She's- She's not-
我不记得...是的，她没来这里
I don't- No. She's not here.
- 你还好吗？ - 是的
- Are you all right? - Yes.
- 很好 - 没骗我吧？
- Yes. - Are you sure?
- 我觉得还行，你呢？ - 我不知道
- I think so. You? - I don't know.
我都不知道怎么办了
I- I just don't know anymore.
我很害怕，卡尔曼，我害怕
I'm scared, Carmen. I'm scared, and, um-
到处是可怕地瘟疫
People are dying from some horrible disease...
还有人在自杀...我怕极了
and others are killing themselves, and... I'm scared.
太可怕了
I'm- I'm scared.
电视没有画面
TV's not workin'.
收音机收不到信号
Radio either.
对了...
Um...
佩特叔叔在哪儿？
where's Uncle Pete?
- 他在... - 佩特，你说佩特啊
- Is he- - Pete- Pete-
佩特在里面的卧室里
Pete's in the back bedroom.
我能去和他说说话吗？
Can I talk to him?
恐怕现在不太合适
Well, I don't know if that's a really good idea right now.
- 为什么？ - 他...
- Why not? - He's-
我也不知道
I don't know.
我们去和他说说话，好吗？
Let's go and talk to him, okay?
可以吗？
Can we do that?
- 我来扶你 - 好吧
- Please. - Well, all right.
我就是...
Uh, I- I'm just-
就是不确定他现在是不是愿意见人
I'm just not sure he wants to talk to anyone right now.
他现在变化挺大的
He really hasn't been himself lately.
帕波先生正和他在一起呢
He has Mr.- Mr. Peppers in there with him. He-
嗯...佩特？
Um- Um- Pete?
老头子
Peter pie.
佩特叔叔？
Uncle Pete?
佩特叔叔,是我，米歇尔
Uncle Pete, it's me. It's Michelle.
你的侄女 米歇尔
It's your niece, Michelle.
有钥匙吗？
Is there a key?
这门从来不锁的
The door doesn't lock. Never has.
那你为什么不进去？
Then why haven't you gone inside?
这个么...
I don't know.
- 别，别进去 - 为什么？
- No, don't. Don't go in there. - Why?
那个东西...
- That's-
那个东西不是我丈夫
That's not my husband.
不再是了
Not anymore.
佩特?
Pete?
天哪，是米歇尔
Oh, my God, Michelle.
你到底怎么了？
What have you done?
贾丝汀?
Justine?
宝贝，是你吗？
Justine, honey. Is that you?
是我，是妈妈
It's me. It's Mommy.
我的宝贝怎么啦？
What's wrong, baby?
你病了吗？
Are you sick?
是不是？
Is that it?
没事的
It's okay.
相信我，不会有事的
Everything's okay. I promise.
能让我看看你吗？
Can I see your face?
转过来让妈妈看看你的脸好吗？
Can you do that for me? Can you show Mommy your face?
- 已经在这里一晚上了 - 什么？
- It's been out here all night. - What?
为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
从太阳下山开始，这东西就一直在那儿看着我
It's been watching me since the sun went down.
- 不要说是“这东西”！ - 刚开始我也以为是贾丝汀
- Stop saying ""it.'' - I- I- I thought it was Justine, too, at first.
但是我反复跟它说了不少
But I tried talking to it.
可它却一句话也没回，而且不给我看它的脸
It never says a word, never shows its face.
米歇尔，我觉得你最好还是离这东西远点
I think you need to get away from it, Michelle. Now.
你说什么啊？难道她...
What are-What are you saying? Is she-
我觉得...如果你碰了这东西...
I think- I think, if you touch it...
你会死的
you-you'll die.
- 不 - 你会被感染的，会死的
- No. - You'll get the infection, and you'll die.
你根本不知道你在说什么胡话
I don't believe you. You don't know what you're saying.
离这东西远点
Get away from it.
宝贝，我们回家吧
Come on, baby. Let's go home.
等等，别走！
Oh, wait. Please wait.
上帝保佑我们
Oh, God have mercy on us all.
God have mercy on us all.
（低语声）不要...不要...不要...
No, no, no.
别走
No, wait, please.
贾丝汀.
Justine.
贾丝汀，快回来
Justine, come back.
求你了！
Please!
我求你了，贾丝汀！
Come back, please,Justine!
贾丝汀！
Justine!
7月6日， 我和学校的教务处谈了话
July 6. I talked to the school psych.
贾丝汀在学校开始有不正常的举动了
Justine is acting out at school.
我和斯蒂芬之间的紧张关系开始影响到孩子身上了
This tension between me and Stephen is affecting our child now.
必须结束这种状况
This has got to stop.
7月15日， 斯蒂芬越来越冷淡
July 1 5. Stephen is more and more remote.
他不在敌视我们，但不和我们说话...
He is no longer hostile, but he won't talk about us...
而且不再去做家庭问题咨询了
and he won't try family counseling.
7月24日
July 24.
我认为斯蒂芬有婚外恋
I think Stephen is having an affair.
8月2日...
August 2...
斯蒂芬提出离婚
Stephen wants a divorce.
说我也有责任
Says I share the blame.
我怎么会为他的过失负责？
How am I to blame for his infidelities?
8月3日 他今天终于搬出去了
August 3. He moved out today.
说是找个小屋独居
Claims he's going to stay at the cabin.
骗子，他和外边那个生活在一起呢
Liar. He's living with her.
我怎么会不明白呢
I know it.
9月14日
September 1 4.
43天的单身生活
Forty-three days single.
和特瑞签订了一份婚介协议
Teri signed me up with a dating service.
那里都是失败者
All losers.
我想你回来，斯蒂芬
I just want you back, Stephen.
9月20日 我沉迷于网聊
September 20. I'm spending all my time in chat rooms.
废寝忘食
I can't eat. I can't sleep.
真是个变态的世界，尤其是在晚上
It's a sick world out there, especially at night.
9月23日 我发现了一个奇怪的网站
September 23. I found a strange Web site.
里面的人看起来好像是在摄像头前面自杀
People actually seem to be killing themselves in front of their webcams.
克服了恐惧之后...
Once I got over the horror of it...
我感觉到了他们的绝望，甚至有些欣赏
I realized there was something almost welcoming in their despair.
分享一种别人理解不了的痛苦
A kind of shared pain nobody else could possibly understand.
9月24日 我必须把这些黑暗的念头从脑子里赶走
September 24. I must get these dark thoughts out of my head.
我得多关心贾丝汀，她是我的小天使
I must think ofJustine. My sweet little angel.
10月5日 我的梦想破灭了
October 5. The day I thought would never come.
斯蒂芬得到了对我们女儿的监护权...
Stephen won custody of our daughter...
而我却被法院裁定为一不称职的母亲
and I was ruled an unfit mother for neglecting my child.
怎么会这样？你怎么能这样对我？我恨你！
How could this happen? How could you do this to me? I hate you.
10月7日 我不能忍受...
October 7. I can't bear the thought...
忍受贾丝汀和你还有那个女人生活在一起
ofleaving Justine with you and that woman.
我宁可我的女儿去死
I would rather see my baby dead.
10月8日 我决定了
October 8. Decision made.
先是贾丝汀...
FirstJustine...
然后是我
then me.
先走好，乖女儿
Good-bye, my love.
我马上和你在一起了
I'll be with you soon.
...一直到永远...
贾丝汀?
Justine?
贾丝汀！贾丝汀！
Justine!Justine!
贾丝汀?
Justine?
贾丝汀！感谢上帝
Justine!Justine, thank God!
你没事吧，我的小甜心？
You all right, sweetheart? You okay?
没事吧？
Huh? You okay?
老天，你可把我急坏了
Christ, I've been worried sick about you.
我给所有邻居打过电话，给911也打了 我还打给了你妈妈
I called all the neighbors. I called 911 . I called your mom.
还有卡尔曼婶婶和佩特叔叔
I called Aunt Carmen and Uncle Pete.
太好了！
Oh!
我的乖宝贝...
Sweetie...
妈妈在哪儿？
where's Mommy?
你知道她在哪里吗？
Huh? Do you know where she is?
她病了吗？
Did- Did she- Did she get sick?
啊？
Huh?
来，让爸爸抱抱，我的小毛孩子
Oh, come here. It's okay, squirt. Daddy's here. There's my big girl.
我们在一起啦
We're together.
没什么会让我们分开的
Nothing's gonna change that. You understand? Nothing.
来吧，我的好女儿
Come on. That's my daughter.
这才是好姑娘
That's my girl.
坐好了
All right. Sit back.
斯蒂芬. 斯蒂芬！
Stephen. Stephen!
贾丝汀.
Justine.
嘿，小丫头
Hey, squirt.
扣上安全带好吗？
You want to buckle up for me?
我来帮你
Here. I'll give you a hand.
好啦
That-a-girl.
真乖
可别啊
Oh, no.
听话，别看
Don't look, okay? Just don't look.
闭上眼睛，我要冲过去
Hold on. I'm gonna try and get past him.
那是贾丝汀吧？
Is thatJustine?
谢天谢地，总算找到你了
You had us all praying for a miracle.
我们大家都在为你祈祷
And praise the Lord, it finally paid off.
你们在这里设置路障吗？
So what's going on? You turning people away now?
只有家人和亲戚能通过这里
Residents and family only. That's the rule.
不然的话，情况会像城里一样失控的
Otherwise it's gonna be chaos, just like down in the city.
应该还有别的办法的
There's gotta be something we can do.
我知道这有点不近人情，但是没有办法
I'm sorry. I know how it sounds, but that's the way it's gotta be.
现在，听好了...
Now, uh-
我要求你和你女儿都下车
I'm gonna have to ask you both to step out of the car.
- 什么意思？ - 你别多想，不过是个预防措施
- What? - Uh, it- it's just a precaution.
不管是谁，只要他离开这里，再回来就得接收检查
Uh, uh, anybody who leaves, don't matter for how long, we just gotta be sure.
- 你到底什么意思，Hutch？ - 仅仅是个防范措施而已
- What's this about, Hutch? - It's just a precaution.
下车吧
Come on.
开什么玩笑啊
You gotta be kidding me.
爸爸抱
Come on.
麻烦你们站到车子前面来
All right. If y'all would just step out the front of the truck here.
把外套脱掉，我们要检查你们的四肢
Take your jackets off. All we need to see is your arms and your legs.
Steve，麻烦你到那一边去
And, Steve, if you'd just go over there.
别怕，宝贝，他是你的Hutch叔叔
All right, sweetheart. It's only Hutch, okay?
没事的，小可爱
It's all right.
把你的双臂亮出来吧
Come on. Let me see your arm.
来吧
Come on.
很好，另一只
All right. Now show me the other arm.
- 现在，叔叔要看看你的小胳膊 - 把裤腿卷一下
- Now your arm. - Now check the leg.
另一条
And the other one.
快来看看，那是什么？
There. What's that?
- 在她的肩膀上 - 那是什么？
- I see it. On her shoulder. - What is that?
- 不过是些脏东西 - 到底是什么，Steve？
- It's dirt. It's just dirt. - What is it, Steve?
- Steve，往后站！ - Hutch你别大惊小怪的！
- Steve, step back. - Christ, Hutch.
- 后退！ - Hutch，这就是些灰尘！
-Just step aside! - Hutch, it's just dirt!
- 他妈的Steve！后退！ - 你再看看，再看！
- Goddamn it, Steve! Step aside! - See? You see?
- 不过是灰尘！ - 好吧
- It's just dirt! - Okay.
- 他妈的就是些灰尘！ - Steve，你给我冷静一下
- It's just dirt, goddamn it! -Just calm down, Steve. All right.
- 行了 - 你们可以通过了
- Okay. - You're good to go.
没事了，Steve
It's good, Steve. It's good.
你想不想和我一起谈谈妈妈？
Do you think you'd like to talk about Mommy?
我不知道
I don't know.
能告诉我发生了什么吗？
Can you tell me what happened?
不着急
Take your time.
她在我的房间里...
She was in my room...
在哭泣
crying.
- 她告诉你原因了吗？ - 她...她...
- Did she say why? - Sh-Sh-
她说不想活了
She said she wanted to die.
她身上全是那种东西
She had that stuff all over her.
什么东西？
What stuff?
黑黑的，像是发霉的枝杈
That black stuff that looks like mold.
她要我...
She wanted me to come-
要我到她身边...
She wanted me to come closer...
但我很害怕
but I was too scared to.
过来宝贝
Come here, baby.
妈妈就想抱抱你
Mommy just wants to hold you.
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
真的太爱你了
It's just 'cause I love you so much.
没事的
It's okay.
不会有事的，宝贝
It's okay, baby.
来吧
Come on.
没事的
It's okay, baby. It's okay.
都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
催眠曲...
# Hush, little baby #
# Don't say a word #
# Mama's gonna buy you #
#A mockingbird #
# If that mockingbird don't sing #
# Mama's gonna buy you a diamond ring #
# If that diamond ring don't shine ##
所有的痛苦都会解脱
All the pain will be gone soon.
很快解脱
- Very soon.
然后我们就能够飞出这里
And then we can fly away from here.
飞翔...
Fly away from-
妈妈？
Mom?
后来怎么样了？
What did you do after that?
你跑开了吗？
Did you run away?
我到卡尔曼婶婶和佩特叔叔家去了
I went to Aunt Carmen's and Uncle Pete's.
我记不起是怎么到那里的
I couldn't remember how to get there.
但我一看到了大教堂...
But then I saw the big church...
就知道该怎么走了
and I remembered where it was.
他们在家吗？
Were they home?
我觉得佩特叔叔在家
I think Uncle Pete was.
但是他待在卧室里不肯出来
But he stayed in his bedroom and wouldn't come out.
于是我就坐在他家后院的秋千上等
So I went out back and sat on a swing and waited for him.
等了多久？
For how long?
- 直到妈妈找过来 - 可是...
- Till Mommy came. - But you-
你是说妈妈去到了卡尔曼婶婶的家里？
You said Mommy came to Aunt Carmen's. Is that what you said?
我想是的
I think so.
什么是“我想是的”？
What do you mean you think so?
对不起，我不该冲你嚷嚷的
Sorry. I didn't mean to raise my voice.
她是不是...
Was she, um-
来吧，丫头
Come on, squirt.
我要给你洗一下，该睡觉了
Let's get you cleaned up and into bed.
晚安，小丫头
Good night, squirt.
- 谁呀？ - 你觉得还会是谁，斯蒂芬？
- Who is it? - Who do you think, Stephen?
向那帮巡逻的混账一再表明， 我还是你的女友
Had to remind those gun-humping mongoloids I was still your girlfriend.
整整3天了，我就像在地狱，可是你在哪儿？
Three days I'm stuck in hell central, and you're where?
- 我去找我的女儿了 - 我就知道
- I was looking for my daughter. - Oh, I get that.
- 那我算什么？ - 能不能先冷静一下
- But what about me? - Could you just take it down a notch?
我觉得我快要死了.斯蒂芬
I thought I was gonna die, Stephen.
我从来没有这么害怕过
I've never been so scared in all my life.
我竟然偷了一辆车...
I had to steal some poor dead fucker's car...
一辆里面充满着车主的灰烬的车！真是太好了！
with his fucking ashes still in it, thank you very much.
一路上孤零零的...
Drive myself up here, alone, hoping and praying...
一路上还得祈祷...
that one of those vigilante alcoholics you call neighbors...
你称之为邻居的那帮酒鬼能够宽容大度地放我进来
will have the simple human decency to let me through.
天哪，我得喝点
God, I need a drink!
干邑、二锅头、五粮液，什么都行
Wine, Drano. Anything.
雪利酒，我想我这儿还有点管饱的东西
I think I have some cooking sherry.
好啊，你有就行
Well, you know how to party.
有高脚杯吗？纸杯也行
Glass? Dixie cup?
算了，直接吹喇叭
Forget it. I'll rough it.
我知道你就在外面
I know you're out there.
你骗不了我
You can't fool me.
我不知道你是谁，但你绝不会是我老婆
I don't know who you are, but you are not my wife.
你听到了没有？
You hear me?
你绝不是我老婆！
You are not my wife!
#地上的纸张上写着：红色可以辟邪# 但是你拿我没招
But you-you can't get me.
你奈何不了我的 （原来老外也相信红色能辟邪:-D）
You can't get me. Huh?
你拿我没招
You can't get me!
#窒息声#
Oh.
坏了...不好了...
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh, God. Oh, God.
我的药片，卡尔曼，我的药片
My pills. My pills. Carmen. Carmen. My pills.
卡尔曼
Car- Carmen?
给我药片，卡尔曼
My pills. Carmen.
卡尔曼，卡尔曼...
Carmen. Carmen. Who-Who-
你是什么东西？
Who are you?
你相信那些关于红色的东西的传言吗？
Do you believe that shit they're saying about the red tape-
据说红色的东西能够保证你的安全
that it keeps you safe somehow?
我都不知道该信些什么了
I'm not sure what to believe anymore.
我可不想到处弄红色的东西， 像把自己封闭在坟墓里似的
Well, I am not sealing myself up in my own tomb.
T太多乱七八糟的传言了
That is just too fucked-up for words.
说到这些，帮我个忙
Speaking of words, do me a favor.
楼上有个6岁大的小丫头...
I have a six-year-old upstairs...
她刚经历了一场孩子不该经历的事情
who's been through something no child should ever have to face.
你能去安抚一下吗？
Could you pleasejust drop a few less F-bombs?
天哪，我根本都没想到这些
God, I hardly even notice anymore.
对不起
Sorry.
对了...
By the way...
- 我知道你在想 - 真的？
- I know what you're thinking. - Really?
- 那我在想什么？ - 你在想我们需要储备多少食物...
- What am I thinking? - You're thinking how much further that food would go...
两个月，也许三个月
with two mouths instead of three.
没想到你还挺能揣摩人
Funny, I never pegged you for a psychic.
你知道我还有一个特别的能力
You know, I could make myself useful.
你这种特别能力能干什么呢？
And how are you gonna do that?
我能让你放松，别人做不来的
I know how to relax you, better than anybody.
哦，别干这个，现在可不行
Oh, please. No. Don't do this. Not now.
不要干嘛？
Don't do what?
- 别！ - 什么？
- Don't! - What?
我们最终走到一起了， 你不觉得我们该庆祝一下吗？
Isn't this how celebretards get out of taxicabs?
- Marta，我理解这些 - 你不理解
- I mean it, Marta. - No, you don't.
你从来没有理解过其中的意义
You never do.
还记得我们第一次偷情吗？
Remember the first time we did it?
就站在你老板的门后面
Standing-
可爱的米歇尔就在外面
on your boss's back porch while dear, sweet Michelle...
和一群人谈论着全球变暖
was inside boring everyone to tears about global warming.
哦，冰开始化了
Wow, the ice is melting, all right.
正贴着我的大腿在溶化
It's trickling right down my thigh.
是你打开的吗？
Okay, did you turn that on?
开玩笑！我才没有
Are you kidding? No way.
你不觉得这很邪乎吗？
Don't you know you're not even supposed to have those things around anymore?
它根本就没接电源
It wasn't even plugged in.
你是不是忘了取下电池了？ （谁也不会有这种习惯啊，明明是Sleep模式被唤醒嘛）
I guess you forgot to pull the battery, now, didn't you?
行了，别说了，你过去看看吧
Well, fine. Be my guest.
我才不碰它
I'm not touching it.
我有两个朋友就是在盆里他们的电脑后自杀的
I had two of my friends kill themselves after touching their computers.
- 你还有朋友？ - 我那个什么你妈，好好说话！
- You had friends? - Okay, ""F'' you, sweetheart.
老天！快采取点什么措施啊！ （网络连接中...）
Jesus.! Do something.
安静！安静！不过就是台电脑而已
Calm down. All right? It's a computer.
你不可能被电脑感染的，那不过是谣言罢了
You can't get infected by a computer. Those are just rumors.
人都变得歇斯底里了
Mass hysteria.
那你去关了它
Well, then you turn it off.
当然可以
Fine. I will.
- 别！ - 怎么啦？
- No, don't! - What?
别直接碰它！
Just don't touch it.
- 你要干什么？ - 杀了它
- What-What are you doing? - Killing it.
等等！
Wait!
天哪
Oh, God.
是米歇尔
It's Michelle.
这是周五发出来的
These are all from Friday.
#救我#
周六也有
There's even more from Saturday.
老天
Jesus.
#还我女儿#
通话结束了！
This session's over.
丫头，我得问你个事儿
Squirt, I need to ask you a question.
很重要，希望你能认真如实的回答我
It's very important that you answer me as honestly and as clearly as you can.
你妈妈还活着吗？
Is Mommy alive?
还是已经死了？
Was she dead?
贾丝汀，你必须告诉我
You have to tell me,Justine.
你最后一次见她的时候，她还活着，对吗？
The last time you saw her, she was alive, right?
她到卡尔曼婶婶家去的时候还是活着的对吗？
When she came to Aunt Carmen's, she was alive.
不，那时候她已经死了
No. She was dead.
#系统恢复...#
#接入互联网#
#回复#
#你在哪儿？#
#邮件已发送#
#还我女儿#
#你在哪里？#
#就在你后面#
爸爸！
Daddy.!
贾丝汀！
Justine.!
Marta，快起来！
Marta, get up.!
- 我们得离开这儿 - 怎么啦，斯蒂芬？
- We gotta get out- - What, Stephen?
- 快，Marta！马上离开 - 斯蒂芬！
- Come on, Marta! Marta, get out now. - Stephen.!
斯蒂芬！
Stephen!
快点！Marta！
Come on! Marta!
Marta！ Marta！
Marta! Marta!
别怕，在这儿等着！
All right, wait here.
Marta！
Marta!
我没有伤害你的意思，是斯蒂芬勾引我的
I didn't mean to hurt you. It wasn't me. It was- Stephen seduced me.
- Marta  - 斯蒂芬救我
- Marta. - Stephen, help me.
快闪！
Move, goddamn it!
妈妈会害我们吗？
Does Mommy want to hurt us?
我想她...
I think she, um-
我想她是太想你了
I think she misses you very much.
我也想她
I miss her too.
尽管我害怕
Even when I'm afraid.
我知道，丫头
I know you do, squirt.
我知道
I know you do.
我们能绕过去吗？
Can we go around it?
总算碰上了，开门！
Jesus. Open the door!
- 把门打开！ - 好吧！
- Open it! - Okay!
后面去，小家伙
Scoot over, Tinker Bell.
- 爸爸 - 右边的距离够了，你可以挤过去
- Daddy. - I left you a gap on the right. You can just squeeze through.
除非你告诉我要干嘛，不然我哪儿都不去
I'm not going anywhere till you tell me what you want.
要么我们就等着前面车的油箱爆炸， 要么你TMD就给我开车！
We can wait for that gas tank to explode, or you can get the hell out ofhere.!
- 换我，就选择后者 - 别拿枪指着我女儿！
- Me, I'd choose the latter. - Get that gun out of my daughter's face!
- 开车 - 好，好
- Just go. - Okay.
没事的，宝贝
Okay, honey, it's okay.
哦，我以为...我是说...
Uh, I- I thought- I-I-I-I mean-
我没想过这里...
I-I-I didn't think anybody was, uh-
这里有这样...
there was anybody, uh-
别走
Don't go.
对不起，我得走了
I'm sorry. Uh, I-I-I should be going.
我以前一直不知道...
I never knew before...
它们的感觉
what they feel.
- 是如此孤独 - 它们？
- So alone. - They?
这位女士，我不知道我能帮你什么...
L-Look, ma'am, I don't know what I can-
老天
Oh, God.
- 你... - 抱我
- U-U-Uh, ma'am- - Touch me.
不
No. Uh-
不，这可不行...
No, m-ma'am. I-I-I'm a- I'm a-
你不想体会，是不是？
You don't want to feel me? Is that it?
是的，哦，不...
Yes- I mean, no.
不是那样的，只是...
I-I-It's not that I don't. I do. I-It's just-
你以为这会传染？（猜的）
You think it's catching?
不是的
It's not.
我不会传染你的
You don't get it from us.
是它们传染你
You get it from them.
也许，我不知道...
Maybe. I- I don't know. I don't-A-A-All I know-
你根本不懂
You know nothing.
你根本不会知道她从我这里夺走了什么
You don't know what she took from me. You don't know.
我很冷
Oh- Oh, I'm so cold.
很冷
So cold.
抱我
Hold me.
就抱抱
Please just hold me.
我太冷了，对
I'm so cold. Yeah.
就抱一抱
You just-just hold me.
求你了
Please.
太冷了
Oh, I'm so cold.
求你了
Please.
抱住我
Please just hold me.
我们先去买些东西
So, we're gonna go on a little shopping trip.
然后我们就分道扬镳，这样好吧？
Then I'm out of your hair for good. How's that?
那些商店几天前就被抢劫一空了
Everything of value was looted days ago.
- 我要找的不是那些东西 - 那究竟是什么？
- Not what I'm looking for. - Which is what, exactly?
这么说吧，我有个计划...
Let's just say that I have a plan...
能够拯救这个世界...
that can save the world...
或者说能够很快结束这一切
or end it a whole lot sooner.
- 拜托，你到底要我干什么？ - 要你开车
- Just tell me what you need me for. - Wheels, man.
- 你准备拯救世界却连辆车也找不到？ - 我从来不开车
- You're planning on saving the world but can't find a car? - I don't drive. I never have.
这是生活环境造成的
It's my bit for the environment.
好了，请下车吧
All right, then, knock yourself out.
不是我，老兄，我不会进去的，是你进去
No, dude, I'm not going in there. You are.
我就跟小丫头呆在这里，你叫什么名字来着？
I'll be sitting right here with little, uh-What's your name?
- 这可不行
- Chatty Cathy
- Chatty Cathy. - No. That is not acceptable.
下车
Get out.
好吧，算你狠，...但总得告诉我要找什么吧
Okay, tell me... exactly what it is I'm looking for.
一种多种用途红外微处理器
It's your basic multi-use infrared microprocessor.
我记得就在某个过道的左边
A few aisles down on the left, as I recall.
一定要记住，型号是IR-245-F
Very important-you want IR-245-F.
记住了？
Comprende?
IR-245-F，好的
IR-245-F. Okay.
- 宝贝别怕... - 去吧
- Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie- - Giddyap.
好吧，丫头
Okay, honey.
爸爸没事的
It's gonna be okay.
好好呆着
You be good.
等一下，我重复一遍，IR-245-F！
Wait, wait, wait, wait. IR-245-F.!
别拿错了
Nothing else will do!
爸爸！
Daddy!
爸爸
Daddy.
开什么玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
#什么时候到达#（仓库内的广播声）
Coming when?
阿弥陀佛...阿弥陀佛...IR-245-F
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. IR-245-F.
IR-245-F.
IR-245-F. IR-245-F. IR-245-F. IR-245-F.
到底在哪儿？
Where are you?
糟了
Oh, shit.
哪里？快啊
What? Come on. What-
"C."
"D."  "E."
天杀的，在哪儿？
Goddamn it! Where?
在这儿，看到了！
All right, here-There! Right there!
快点啊！
Come on!
不！
No.!
滚开！
Get away from me.!
宝贝坐进去一些
Get over, sweetheart.
你拿到了？
Did you get it?
- 是的 - 过来
- Yeah. - Come here.
好了
Right on.
我昨晚看见我前妻了
I saw my ex-wife last night.
- 愉快吧 - 我的已经死了的前妻
- What a joy. - My dead ex-wife.
所以你想知道...
So you want to know...
她在哪儿，为什么回来...
where she's been, why she's back...
即便这真的是她
and if it's really even her.
好吧，想像一下你在一片黑暗、空虚中漂浮
All right. Imagine you're out there floating in some black, empty void.
突然出现了一条路
Suddenly there's a way back to this plane of existence...
一条回到这个世界的路
a way back to life.
你一定会走进去的，是不是？
You'd grab onto it, wouldn't you?
即便你已经不属于这个世界了
Even if that life wasn't your own?
问题是，在这出激情演出里，你仍然是死了的
The problem is, in this little passion play you're still not alive.
这就会出大问题
And that's gotta hurt.
真是非常糟糕...
That's gotta really suck...
你就会想尽一切办法要重生...
to know that you made it all the way back...
最终只会发现...
only to find out, beyond a shadow of a doubt...
你毫无疑问还是死了的
that you're still fuckin' dead.
拿着，它们无法穿透红色的东西
Here. Take it. Red's the one frequency they can't penetrate.
我也听说过
Yeah, I kinda got that impression.
那我要怎么用它？
So what am I supposed to do with this?
到时候你就明白了
When the time comes, you'll think of something.
- 爸爸 - 留在车里
- Dad. - Stay in the car.
乖，待车里
Stay in the car.
#请找服务人员#
我一会就回来
Be right back.
请问？
Excuse me?
我要加油
I'd like to buy some gas.
嗨？
Excuse me?
哥们？
Sir?
我在4号加油机
I'm on pump four.
我只是...
I'm just g-
我进来了
I'm just stepping inside.
我要...
I'm just gonna-
我要把手...
I'm just gonna reach past you...
从你的上面伸过去
over your shoulder.
仅此而已
That's it. That's all.
这样...
I'll, uh-
我会把钱放在加油机上的
I'll leave the cash on top of the pump, if that's all right with you.
打开油箱盖
Pop the gas cap.
知道在哪里吗？
You know where it is, right?
还是我来吧
Never mind. I got it.
就在这
There.
我没有不给钱的意思
I-I-I had no intention of stealing your gas.
这里不自助的
It's full service only.
明白了
Oh. Right.
呃
Uh-
没问题，那就加油吧
Hey, that works for me. No problem.
这里只剩下高标号的了
Uh, premium's all I got left.
好，高标号的不错
Fine. Uh, p-p-premium's- premium's fine.
很好
It's b- better than fine.
我太感谢你了
You have no idea how grateful I am.
确切说，是感谢这些高标号汽油
I was, uh, practically on fumes.
坐过去，丫头
Move over, squirt.
知道这附近有救济中心之类的地方吗？
Do you happen to know anything about any kind of relief center?
类似紧急避难场所之类的
Emergency services, anything like that?
在306公路边上有个难民营
There's a- a refugee camp being set up along 306.
在Chillicothe南面20英里的样子
It's about 20 miles south of Chillicothe.
那里是手机型号的盲区
It's where the cell signals won't reach.
谢了，我这就奔那里去
Thanks. I'll try heading down that way.
丫头，我们还要开4个小时就到了
Hey, did you hear that, squirt? It's only four or five hours' drive from here.
到那里又有他妈的屁用
Not that it'll do you a damn bit of good.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
那里一定有吃有睡
I'm sure they got food and a place to sleep.
- 我打赌那里肯定还有和你差不多大的孩子 - 那妈妈呢？
- I bet they even have other kids your age. - What about Mommy?
我想她一定不想你为她担心...
I'm sure that she would want you to be okay...
希望你开开心心的
before she'd ever want you worrying about her.
妈妈都这样的
That's just the way mommies are.
我知道这不容易...
I know it's hard, but... try to-
嗨！干嘛？
Hey. Hey!
等一下
Wait. Wait.
糟糕！
Oh, shit.
他妈的
Damn it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
会有人来的
Someone will come along to help us.
我真只需要坐着等待
We just have to sit tight.
一路上我一个人也没见到
I haven't seen anybody else.
你呢？有一段时间了
Have you? Not for a long time.
明天早上我们就会再上路的
Look, by tomorrow morning we'll be back on the road.
我们只要找到难民营就行了
We just have to find this refugee camp.
只有个把小时的路程
It's- It's only a- It's only a couple of hours away.
什么叫难民？
What's a refugee?
就是...
It's, um-
就是有部分人...
It's someone who, um-
见鬼，谁会喜欢去难民营呢
Well, who likes to camp.
知道吗？
You know what?
我们得睡会儿了
We should try to get some sleep, squirt.
我害怕，睡不着
I'm too scared to sleep.
别怕
Oh, come on.
就像去年夏天在国王峡谷
Just like last summer. King's Canyon?
雨打在帐篷上沥沥作响...
When it rained so hard on the tent...
你要睡在车里
you wanted to go sleep in the car.
就像那一样
It's just like that.
- 好不好？ - 好的
- Okay? - Okay.
好女孩
That's my girl.
那是什么？
What is it?
你看到什么了？
What do you see?
没什么，我只是...
It's nothing. I'm just, um-
只是在想事情
You know,just-just thinking.
我有个主意
You know what? I got an idea.
拿着
Here.
- 把这头黏在那上面 - 好嘞
- Fix that up there. - Okay.
- 上面 - 嗯
- Up here. - Hmm?
- 那里 - 还有那里
- There. - There.
对了
That's it.
- 这是要干嘛？ - 我们要做一个帐篷
- What are we doing? - We are making a tent.
你在保护我们的安全，是不是？
You're trying to keep us safe, aren't you?
是的
That's right.
- 为了防妈妈？ - 为了...
- From Mommy? - From...
不管是什么
whatever.
好了
There.
这个帐篷怎么样？
How's that for a tent?
Marta说她做的最后一件事就是 把自己封闭在自己的坟墓里
Marta said the last thing she would ever do was seal herself up in her own tomb.
是的
Yeah.
- 但这可不一样 - 为什么？
- Well, it's not like that. - Why not?
因为这不是坟墓
Because it's not.
好吧...
Ah-
乖乖睡觉吧
Go on to sleep, all right?
安静
Okay?
晚安，小丫头
Good night, squirt.
贾丝汀.
Justine.
爸爸？
Dad?
爸爸
Dad.
嗯？怎么了？
Hmm? What is it?
睡觉吧
Go back to sleep, squirt.
爸爸
Dad.
没什么，贾丝汀
It's nothing,Justine.
只有风的声音
It's just the wind.
贾丝汀.
Justine.
妈妈？
Mommy?
我想你，太想你了
I miss you. I miss you so much.
贾丝汀！
Justine!
贾丝汀，听见了吗？
Justine, can you hear me?
贾丝汀，快回来！
Justine, get back here!
贾丝汀，听见了就喊一声
Justine, shout if you can hear me!
贾丝汀！
Justine.!
妈妈？
Mommy?
宝贝你听见了吗？
Honey, can you hear me?
贾丝汀！
Justine!
不，不要！贾丝汀！
No, don't.! Don't.! Justine.!
那不是你妈妈 贾丝汀
Th-That is not your mother,Justine.!
老天，快过来！
Oh,Jesus.! Come here.!
过来，贾丝汀！
Come on,Justine.!
妈妈！我要妈妈！
Mommy.! I want my mommy.!
我要妈妈！ 我要妈妈！
I want my mommy! I want my mommy!
呆在这里！
Stay put!
不！我要出去！
No! Let me out!
- 贾丝汀，听话，贾丝汀！ - 让我出去！让我出去！我恨你！我恨你！
- Justine- Please,Justine! - Let me out! Let me out! I hate you! I hate you!
- 听话，贾丝汀！贾丝汀！听话！ - 我恨你！
- Please,Justine!Justine, please! Listen! - I hate you!
- 这都是你的错！是你害死了妈妈！ - 那不是你妈妈！
- It's your fault! You killed Mommy! - That is not your mommy!
- 闭嘴！好啦！贾丝汀！ - 你害死了妈妈！
- Shut up! Please! Please!Justine! - You killed Mommy!
- 闭嘴！别说了！ - 我恨你！
- Shut up! Shut up! - I hate you!
上帝！我这是干什么！ 我干了什么！上帝！
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my- Oh, my God!
听我说，对不起！贾丝汀！求你了！
Hey. Hey, hey, hey. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Justine, please! Please!
我的毛丫头，爸爸对不起你！
Oh, God. Oh, God, squirt. I'm sorry.
爸爸不是那个意思！不是那意思！
Squirt, I didn't mean that. I didn't mean that.
不要误会，好吗？对不起！
I didn't mean to do that. Okay? I'm sorry.
爸爸对不起你
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, okay?
爸爸真的很抱歉
Daddy's really sorry.
我宁愿...
I will never-
如果我一直和她在一起...
If I went with her...
也许她就不会那样悲伤...
she wouldn't be so sad...
是不是？
would she?
你害死了她
You killed her.
不是的，贾丝汀
No,Justine.
是的，这都是你的错
Yes, you did. Your fault.
那是什么？
What's that?
过来，对不起
Come here. I'm so sorry.
实在很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
贾丝汀，醒醒
Justine, wake up.
拜托了，快停下！
Come on, stop!
老天爷，帮帮忙吧
Please, please, please.
阿弥陀佛
Oh, my God.
听着，你们将会被转运到一个安全地带...
Attention. You will be transferred to a secure location...
在蜂窝覆盖区之外 不知道是移动的还是联通的网络
outside existing cellular coverage zones.
所有避难者都将获得必要的食品、衣物以及药品...
All transferees will be supplied food, shelter and necessary provisions...
一直到危机结束
till the crisis is past.
丫头，快看，那边有辆大巴车
Hey, squirt, come here. Squirt, there is a bus out there.
我们可以离开这里了
It is our ticket out of here. Okay?
我一喊你跑，你就向那辆大巴跑过去
When I give you the word, I need you to run straight for the bus.
好不好？
You can do that?
- 嗯 - 好孩子
- Mm-hmm. - Good girl.
过来，爸爸会在你后面的
Come on. Come over here. Daddy's got you.
跑！！
Okay, run. Run!
贾丝汀，只管跑！
Justine, keep going!
跑吧，丫头！快跑！
Come on, squirt! Run! Run! Come on!
你不能停下，快跑！
You can do it. You can do it, kid. Come on.
别停下，快跑，别管它！
Come on. Come on. Come on.
- 贾丝汀，快跑！ - 她需要我
- Justine, come on! - She needs me.
不是的，贾丝汀
No.Justine.
她已经死了，无论怎样，我们都无法改变这点
She is dead, and there's nothing that we can do that can change that.
听着
Come on.
贾丝汀，看着我
Justine, look at me.
我保证会弄对这一切的
I will make this right. I promise I will make this right.
你必须相信我
Y-You have to believe in me.
行吗？
C-Can you do that?
我要你直接跑到大巴车里面去
Then I need you to run straight to the bus.
无论如何不要回头
And whatever you do, never look back.
好不好？
Okay?
我会用整个生命来爱你的
I love you with all my heart.
我也爱你，爸爸
I love you too, Daddy.
好的
Okay.
现在，跑，我就在你后面
Now go. I'll be right behind you.
就在你后面
I'm right behind you.
我爱你...
I love you...
永远
always.
爸爸！爸爸！
Daddy! Daddy!
爸爸！
Daddy!
- 坚持住！不用那么快 - 让我走！
- Hold on, little soldier! Not so fast. - Let me go!
- 不行，你得跟我们在一起！ - 放开我！
- No, no. You're coming with us! - Let me go!
- 让我走！ - 你得跟我们在一起
- Let me go! - You're coming with us, sweetie.
不！
No.!
我知道你不会罢休的，米歇尔
I know you'll never stop, Michelle.
这个世界上根本没有能让我们的女儿忘记去找你的地方...
And there's no place that I can take our daughter where she won't try to find you...
你也一样
and you her.
如果你要惩罚我以前的所作所为...
So if you feel that you need to punish me for what it is that I've done...
或者需要找个人来分担那份孤独...
or if you just want someone to share the loneliness...
那么...
then...
就让我来吧
I'll come with you.
你可以带走我
You can take me.
但是只带走我
But please take me alone.
- 为了贾丝汀，我求你了 - 爸爸！
- I'm begging you. ForJustine. - Daddy.!
爸爸！
Daddy!
Dad!
- 爸爸！ - 为了你的女儿
- Daddy.! - For your daughter.
为了我们的那个小女孩
For our- For our little girl.
求你了
Please.
- 和我们在一起，我保证你会没事的 - 不！ 不 不
- You'll be okay with us. I promise. - No! No. No.
- 我们会带着你... - 不！ 不！
- Gonna take you- - No! No!
你会没事的 我保证我们会照顾你的
You'll be okay. We'll take care of you. I promise you.
- 不！ - 我抓住他了
- No! - I got her. I got her.
我一直爱着你的，米歇尔
I always loved you, Michelle.
永远的
Always and forever.
谢谢你
Thank you.
啊
Ah.
小宝贝，现在会很难受的
It hurts now, sweetheart.
但总会过去的
It won't always.
时间轴、特效双语:lengshan310